<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CrimeGuardian</string>
    <string name="assault">assault</string>
    <string name="text_crime_1">There was a brutal murder</string>

    <string name="text_crime_2">Almaty police reported a 34% drop in crime rates</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="extra_call">extra call</string>
    <string name="text_call">Рhone number of a trusted person</string>
    <string name="contact_name">Арай Уали</string>
    <string name="phone_number">+77087377737</string>
    <string name="theft">Theft</string>
    <string name="burglary">Burglary</string>
    <string name="text_crime_3">A man wanted for murder shot and killed a man in Almaty</string>
    <string name="text_crime_4">\nAlmaty police found a stolen SUV</string>
    <string name="search_for_an_address">Search for an address</string>
    <string name="response_geojson">response.geojson</string>
    <string name="source">source</string>
    <string name="author">author</string>
    <string name="instruction1">Knowing the Law</string>
    <string name="shortDescription">Know the Law: Familiarize yourself with the laws and regulations applicable in your area, including local, state, and federal laws. Understand what actions are considered criminal offenses and the potential consequences associated with them.\nExercise Self-Control: Before acting, pause and consider the potential outcomes of your actions. Avoid impulsive behavior that may lead to criminal activity. Take responsibility for your choices and their impact on others.\nRespect Others: Treat others with dignity and respect. Avoid actions that harm or infringe upon the rights of others, whether it\'s physical harm, theft, fraud, or other forms of misconduct.\nSeek Legal Advice: If you\'re uncertain about the legality of a certain action or situation, seek guidance from legal professionals or trusted authorities. Don\'t hesitate to ask questions and clarify any doubts you may have.\nResolve Conflicts Peacefully: When faced with conflicts or disagreements, seek peaceful resolutions through communication and negotiation. Avoid resorting to violence, intimidation, or coercion to resolve disputes, as these actions can lead to criminal charges.\nBe Honest and Ethical: Maintain honesty and integrity in your interactions with others. Avoid engaging in deceptive or fraudulent activities, such as lying, cheating, or stealing, which are often considered criminal offenses.\nSurround Yourself with Positive Influences: Surround yourself with friends, family, and mentors who uphold ethical values and discourage criminal behavior. Positive influences can help reinforce good decision-making and deter you from engaging in unlawful activities.\nTake Responsibility for Your Actions: If you make a mistake or unintentionally break the law, take responsibility for your actions. Cooperate with law enforcement authorities if necessary and work towards rectifying the situation and avoiding similar mistakes in the future.</string>
    <string name="actors">ActorList</string>
    <string name="Actor1">actor1</string>
    <string name="Actor2">actor2</string>
    <string name="Actor3">actor3</string>
    <string name="Actor4">actor4</string>
</resources>
